Inventory of the Slavic Book Dealer Catalogs
Department of Special Collections
- Catalogs: "Szwede Slavic Bookstore" (Palo Alto, CA), 2003 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Catalogs: "Szwede Slavic Bookstore" (Palo Alto, CA), 2004 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Catalogs: "Szwede Slavic Bookstore" (Palo Alto, CA), 2005 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Catalogs: "Szwede Slavic Bookstore" (Palo Alto, CA), 2006 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Catalogs: "Szwede Slavic Bookstore" (Palo Alto, CA), 2007 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Catalogs: "Szwede Slavic Bookstore" (Palo Alto, CA), n.d. (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Catalogs: Katalog Knizhok: "Ukrainskaia knygarnaia v Edmontoni". Edmonton, AB: 2001-2002, no. 63; 2009, no. 67 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Catalogs of "The Keys [Kliuchy]: Ukrainian Publishing Assn.", n.d. (Box 86, Folder 12)
- Catalogs of "Verlag Otto Sanger: Lieferbare Titel. Kubon & Sagner". Munchen, Germany: January 2000, Literaturwissenschaft: Russland/Nachfolgestaaten UdSSR: vols. 1-2, May 2010; also, correspondence - 2010. (Box 86, Folder 13)
- East View [a book dealer]. Minneapolis, MN materials: calendar for 2002, correspondence - 2010. (Box 86, Folder 14)
- Bernard Quaritch LTD. London, UK: two catalogs: Russian books, 2010/12 and European & South American Literature, 2010/4 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- Catalogs of Polish bookstores: "Polish Antiquarian Books: Antykwariat Wspolczesny". Brooklyn, NY: Grudzien 1997, no. 10; Polish Bookstore "Ksiegarnia Literacka". Brooklyn, NY: catalog polskiej ksiegarni wysylkowej: Winter-Spring 2003, no. 29 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  Also, "Globus". San Francisco, CA: catalogs of 2001 & 2010.
- Sims Reed Rare Books. London, UK: catalogs: Modern Illustrated Books and A selection of Rare Books. (Box 86, Folder 17)
- Catalogs of various book dealers: "Erasmus Verlag". Zagreb, Chroatia; "Ediciones del Hebreo Errante". Madrid, Spain; "Dr. Anton Kovac". Munchen, Germany: Spring 2010; "Slavonica"; 2008 bookmark by "MIPP"; booklet: Bookstores in the Toronto area: supplying Central and East European material; "Knjiga trgovina" - correspondence, 2010; "Kozmenko Booksellers": CD list from Natasha Kozmenko; "Antiquarian books and music" - Simon Beattie - correspondence and catalog: 2010; "Theodore Front Musical Literature" catalog, n.d.; "Hemus Partners Co Ltd" - correspondence; "North Star Books". Montreal, Canada - catalog, 2001; "Ross Publishing LLC": correspondence and catalog, 2010. (Box 86, Folder 18)
- Productive Arts: Russian & Soviet Posters, Graphic & Publications. Irvine, CA: catalogs, nos. 7-10, correspondence, graphic materials. (Box 86, Folder 19)
- List of the bookstores in the San Francisco Bay Area. (Box 86, Folder 20)
- Correspondence with Czeslaw Milosz. (Box 86, Folder 21)
- List of Szwede Bookstore's customers in the U.S. (Box 86, Folder 22)
- Correspondence with customers: 2003-2010, including letter from PIASA (Polish Institute of Art and Science of America). (Box 86, Folder 23)
- Correspondence with Ars Polona, a Polish book dealer and Ars Polona catalog, 2009 (Box 86, Folder 24)
- Publications about Szwede Slavic Bookstore by Wojciech Zalewski. (Box 86, Folder 25)
- Personal and financial documents of Irena Szwede. (Box 86, Folder 26)
- Financial books of the Bookstore: 1999-2002 (2 books). (Box 86, Folder 27)